now that we have seen our new machinery
let's talk about how we manage power
even though we are connecting a lot of machines
a 4 amps cable is enough
because that's the maximum amperage we are producing
that power is provided by four steam turbines
each one can use slightly more than 1500 steam per second
so a potin pipe with a flow speed of 6000 steam per second should be just enough
talking of power flow
our cables have a loss of 1 EU per block
which means that we are losing voltage for each additional piece of cable we use
this has two main consequences
the first one is a loss of energy
the second one is that a single turbin could no longer be enough
but that's more advanced the stuff
all of that is just to say that
you should try to keep the most power intensive machines close to the generators
to run the heaviest recipes we are using a lot of steam
all of that steam comes from burning random stuff in our expanded railcraft boiler
it is now composed of 12 tanks
meaning it can produce 120 steam per tick
2,400 per second
that's less than half of our needs
but since we won't be running constantly at peak consumption
we can fix everything with a bigger buffer
and once we managed to stock up some steam
we can start using our workshop
the first thing we will want to do
is to stock up some of the most used parts
starting from copper wire steel plates and thin cables
since we will need lots of those parts
we have equipped those machines with hoppers
to do bigger and unsupervised batches
and to avoid overfilling the output chests
we keep some of the excess stuff in some drawers close by
now that we stocked up the basic parts
let's craft a batch of circuits
to help us keep track of the missing materials
we bookmark recipes ingredients in NEI
we do that recursively for all of the stuff we haven't stocked up
such as resistors
which we can now craft in a more efficient way with an assembler
there we also notice that we can double our yield by running copper through an arc furnace to anneal it
next we can improve our vacuum tube production process
by using molten metal and annealed copper
once we bookmarked all of the main steps we will be doing
we can link those together
and apply the batch multiplier we want to achieve
now we just have to collect those ingredients
and Mark them off once acquired
and to speed up
we can try to do multiple things at once
that's why we also have some duplicated machines
and that's how we can now quickly craft a batch of circuits
but before using those for new machinery
we should get a better source of fuel for our boiler
there are a lot of different fuels
with many different ways of production
but for now we can stick with wood
so far we have been gathering it by manually chopping down trees
but we want a lower effort solution
we can do that in many different ways
the first one we will see is by using Steve's carts
as the name suggests
this involves some highly customizable minecarts
which we shall equip with a wood cutter to achieve our objective
assembling this cart will take quite some time
which you can use to prepare a track where it will be working
once everything is ready we can place our cart
give it fuel
and admire our new automated wood source
at first sight it may looks slow and with low output
but don't be fooled by appearances
you can verify that it is indeed slightly better than a flint axe by looking at its internal storage while it does its job
it also has more durability than a flint axe
speed aside
what matters is that it will autonomously bring wood to our base
to increase the combustion of this wood
we can pass it through an array of coke ovens to make charcoal
which we can then compress into blocks
now if you do not like to have a moving car that requires periodic diamond repairs
I have another option for you
forestry farms
those run on cheaper materials
but have a lot of moving parts
if you want a zero maintenance system
that also has not constant block by block collection
I suggest moving on to ic2 crops
which outscores the other two systems in every way
except for aesthetics
but the real potential of ic2 crops lies in cross breeding and ore berries
and here we can see a cultivation of aluminum and gold
from seeds given by the quest book
on a side note
the fruit of those berries can be collected from when the plant reaches the third stage of growth
we could get a better yield by waiting for the fourth and last stage of growth
but for that the crops need a block of metal underneath
which we cannot afford yet
and the issue is that
our crop manager will be waiting for that unreachable stage of growth
that means we will have to manually collect those for now
later on we will automate the collection by having a block of metal underneath
like we already did with gold
our crop manager also needs a little bit of power
and we are feeding it with a super thin cable
this is a chip cable which has no loss
meaning we can make it as long as we like
the downside is that it can only carry 8 volts
meaning we need a transformer
this transformer will output up to 4 amps
and since our crop manager can probably take at least 2 amps
we could end up burning the thin 1 amp cable
to ensure we do not exceed the maximum amperage
we can use cable diodes
in this case a ULV Machine Hull
with that we are running this cheap cable at its limit 8 EU per tick
which is enough to harvest 40 crops per second
the next thing we should probably try to get is some aluminum ingots
both to fully automate our crops
and to move on to the next age
this requires an electric blast furnace
and the main challenge here is that
some people could have issues locating a mica vein
one low effort foolproof way to do that is to
first take a walk on some mountains with a ore finder wand looking for pure tin
this will find us a cassiterite vein
from which we can take some samples of cassiterite ore
not to be confused with cassiterite sand
now that we have cassiterite ore we can easily locate mica
meaning we can build an EBF
and this machine is going to be one more wiring challenge
that's because most of its processes will require 120 EU per tick
and even one less will cause the machine to fail and void items
to achieve such power
we will need at least 4 amps of low voltage
as we have already seen
the issue is cable power loss
and if we are not careful
we could easily fail to meet the requirements
sometimes that could be just as easy as disconnecting a single cable connection
and we must also not forget to use a good enough pipe to feed those turbines
on a side note
I often get asked why I always restricted pipe flow direction
and this is one other thing that may change between updates and gregtech versions
but from testing it right now
I will say that for a point to point pipe
it doesn't really make much of a difference
however if we add some dead end modification
we can start to see some backflow
that will slow down the main pipe flow
I will say that you should do that just to make the behavior more predictable
now that we have a working EBF and aluminum
we can also get gallium arsenide
in order to make the new type of circuit
thus moving to the MV age
so after getting a circuit assembler
to cut the cost of making more circuits
we rushed our first MV machine
an extruder
we really want this machine as soon as possible
because it will make crafting parts way easier and cheaper
next before doing more progress in this tire
we should fix our energy production
we could upgrade our Railcraft boiler or get more solar boilers
but an interesting option is also the bronze boiler
this one can make enough steam to power 3 blast furnaces
and reaches working temperature in less than a minute
making fuel management easier
with that we can now get into MV tasks
or better yet
let's start from automating stuff we could have done in the previous tire
现在我们已经看到了新机器
是时候讲讲电力管理的事情了
尽管已经连接了很多机器
但一根4A的线缆便已足够
因为这是我们目前的发电上限
由四台蒸汽轮机提供
其每秒大约消耗1500L蒸汽
所以蒸汽流量6000L/s的粗青铜合金已经足够了
说到电力传输
我们的电缆每格损失1EU
这意味着我们每使用一根额外的电缆就会失去电压
这有两个主要后果
第一个是能量损失
第二个是一个涡轮已经不够用了
但那是更进阶的东西
总的来说
最耗电的机器应该贴近发电机
为了运行最耗电的配方，我们使用了大量的蒸汽
所有的蒸汽都来自于RC锅炉燃烧掉的随机可燃物
它现在有12台储罐
这意味着它每tick可以生产120L蒸汽
2400L每秒
这还不到我们需求的一半
不过我们可不会一直处于消耗巅峰
我们可以用更大的缓冲来解决所有问题
一旦我们设法储备了一些蒸汽
我们可以开始使用我们的车间
我们要做的第一件事
就是储备一些最常用的零件
从铜线缆、钢板和细电缆开始
因为我们会大量需要这些零件
我们已经为那些机器配备了漏斗
用来完成更大批量的被动生产
同时为了避免输出箱被填满
我们把多余的东西放在附近的抽屉里
现在我们储备了基本零件
让我们制作一批电路
要让我们能追踪缺少的材料
我们在NEI中为配方增加合成链
我们对所有没有储备的东西都递归地这样做
比如我们现在可以用组装机来增产的电阻
我们还注意到，通过将铜放入电弧炉退火
我们可以将电阻的产出翻倍
接下来我们可以通过使用熔融金属和
退火铜来改进真空管生产工艺
一旦我们将要做的所有主要步骤都标记
我们可以把它们联在一起
并施加我们想要实现的批乘数
现在我们只需要收集那些原料
获得之后就把它们取消标记
而为了加快速度
可以尝试同时做多件事
这就是为什么我们也有一些相同的机器
这就是我们现在快速制作一组电路的方法
但在将它们用于新机器之前
我们应该为锅炉找到更好的燃料来源
燃料很多
也有很多不同的产出方法
但现在可以继续使用木头
到目前为止，我们一直通过手工来砍伐
但我们想要一个麻烦更少的方案
有许多方法
第一个是通过使用史蒂夫矿车模组
顾名思义
这涉及到一些高度可定制的矿车
我们将为它配备一个伐木器来实现我们的目标
组装这辆车需要相当长的时间
我们利用这段时间在它工作的地方铺设好轨道
一旦一切准备就绪，我们就可以放置矿车了
加入燃料，欣赏我们新的自动化木材来源
乍一看，它可能看起来很慢，输出也很低
但不要被外表所迷惑
你可以通过查看它的内部存储来验证
它确实比燧石斧稍微好一点
它也比燧石斧更耐用
抛开速度不谈，重要的是
它会自动把木头带到我们的基地
想增加木头的燃烧时间
可以让它通过焦炉来制造木炭
然后我们可以将其压缩成块
现在如果你不喜欢拥有一个
需要定期使用钻石维修的矿车
这有另一个选择
林场
它使用更便宜的材料
但有很多活动部件
如果你想要一个零维护系统
也无需具体的方块收集
我建议转向ic2作物
它在各个方面都胜过其他两个系统
除了美学
但ic2作物的真正潜力在于杂交育种和矿石浆果
这里我们可以看到由任务书
赠送的种子种下的铝和金矿莓
顺便说一句
这些矿莓的果实可以从植物生长到第三阶段时收集
也可以等待其到第四阶段来获得更多产物
但庄稼下面需要放一个金属块才能进入那一阶段
我们还负担不起那些
问题是我们的作物管理器
会等待那个遥不可及的生长阶段到来
这意味着我们现在必须手动收集这些
稍后，我们将通过在下面放一块金属来自动收集
就像我们已经对黄金做的那样
我们的作物管理器也需要一点电
我们用一根超细电缆供电
这是一根很便宜的超导线缆
意思是我们想搞多长就多长
缺点是它最大电压只有8V
这意味着我们需要一个变压器
该变压器将输出高达4A的电流
由于我们的作物管理器可能至少需要2A
这种细线缆可能会被烧了
为了确保我们不超过最大电流
我们可以使用电缆二极管
在这种情况下，是ULV机器外壳
有了它，其最大功率便被限制在8EU/t
这足以每秒收获40株作物
接下来我们可能应该尝试购买一些铝锭
都是为了让我们的作物完全自动化
为进入下一个时代
这需要一个电高炉
这里的主要挑战是
有些人可能在定位云母矿脉时遇到问题
一个不需要努力且万无一失的方法是
首先带着找寻矿魔杖在山上寻找纯锡
这能找到锡石矿脉
我们可以从中提取一些锡石矿石样本
不要与锡石砂混淆
而有了锡，云母矿脉便不在话下
这意味着我们可以做一个EBF
这台机器将是另一个布线挑战
这是因为它的大部分配方都需要120EU/t
即使少一点也会导致机器故障并使物品被吞
要达到这样的功率，至少要4A的LV电
正如我们已经看到的
问题是线损
如果我们不小心
很容易达不到要求
有时这可能就像断开单个电缆连接一样简单
我们也不能忘记使用足够好的管道来为涡轮机供电
顺便说一句
我经常被问到为什么我总是限制管道流动方向
这是另一件可能在不同更新
或不同GT版本之间发生变化的事
但从现在的测试来看
我会说点对点管道
这没什么区别
但是如果我们添加一些死胡同
我们可以看到一些倒流
这将降低主管道的流量
我会说为了让流动更可预测，你应该这么做
现在我们有一个正常工作的EBF和铝
我们还能弄到砷化镓
用来制造新型电路
从而进入MV时代
所以在拿到能降低制造更多
电路板成本的电路组装机后
我们速通出第一台MV机器——压模机
这台机器真的越早出越好
因为这将使制作零件变得更容易、更便宜
在这个阶段取得更多进展前
我们应该修复能源生产
我们可以升级RC锅炉或制作更多太阳能锅炉
但另一个有趣的选择是青铜锅炉
这个可以产生足够的蒸汽来驱动3个高炉
并在一分钟内达到工作温度
而使燃料管理变得轻松
有了它，我们现在可以进入MV任务
或者最好先不进入
让我们先从上一电压本就可以做的自动化开始吧